http://www.statesurge.com/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
StateSurge understands how important the privacy of personal information is to our users. This Privacy Policy will tell you what information we collect about you and about your use of the StateSurge website and its services. It will explain the choices you have about how your personal information is used and how we protect that information. We urge you to read this Privacy Policy carefully. This Privacy Policy applies to the StateSurge Website owned and operated by LobbyAssist LLC. By using this site, you signify your assent to the terms of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to all of these terms, do not use this site.   General LobbyAssist, Inc. ("LobbyAssist, " or "StateSurge") owns and operates the StateSurge website. LobbyAssist may revise and update this Privacy Policy at any time. Your continued usage of the StateSurge website ("StateSurge Site," or the "Site,") will mean you accept those changes. All products and services on the StateSurge Site are made available subject to this Privacy Policy. By using the products and services, you agree, without limitation or qualification, to be bound by this Privacy Policy. Questions regarding this statement should be directed to: Attn: Office of Privacy
393 Euclid Ave, Suite 653
Saint Louis, MO 63108 contact@statesurge.com   What information does LobbyAssist collect The StateSurge servers automatically log certain information that StateSurge uses for statistical analysis of web site traffic. The information is stored as log files on the StateSurge server system. The log files are regularly collected and analyzed by software to produce visitor trend reports. The information that is collected includes:
Your IP Address The length of time you stayed on the Site Where you came into the Site Where you left the Site The referring Site that sent you to StateSurge The type of browser you are using
This information is used to determine:
Traffic Patterns Average visitor session length Number of visitors to certain areas of the site Other user trends
Server logs do not contain personally identifiable information on individual users, such as names, addresses, email address, occupation, etc. This type of data will only be collected in forms, surveys or user registrations on StateSurge's Site.   Personally identifiable information StateSurge also collects personally identifiable information that you voluntarily submit through online forms on our website, such as:
Name Postal Address E-mail Address
How does StateSurge use the information it collects StateSurge collects information to provide you with the services you request and to improve our website. StateSurge also uses this aggregate, anonymous data to perform statistical analysis of the collective characteristics and behavior of our site visitors; to measure user interests regarding specific areas of StateSurge Site; and to analyze how and where best to use our resources. Without such data, we would not know which parts of StateSurge's Site are the most popular, and we would not be able to change and update the content and services appropriately. StateSurge may be required by law enforcement or judicial authorities to provide information on individual users to the appropriate governmental authorities. In matters involving a danger to personal or public safety, StateSurge may voluntarily provide information to appropriate governmental authorities. When you provide personally identifiable information on StateSurge's Site to register for service, buy a product, or take advantage of a promotion, that information is collected and maintained solely by StateSurge, unless specifically stated otherwise at the point of collection. StateSurge does not sell member e-mail addresses to third-parties.   What are cookies and how does StateSurge use them A cookie is a small text file containing a unique identification number that is transferred from a website to the hard drive of your computer. This unique number identifies your web browser, but not you to StateSurge computers whenever you visit the StateSurge Site. A cookie will not provide personally identifiable information about you, such as your name and address. The use of cookies is now an industry standard, and cookies are currently used on most major websites. Most web browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. If you prefer, you can reset your browser to notify you when you have received a cookie. You can also set your browser to refuse to accept cookies altogether. While disabling cookies is possible, keep in mind that StateSurge does require cookies to be enabled for most services to function properly. Generally, cookies enable our server to remember visitors, allow entry into password-protected areas, and to help ensure accurate measuring of web traffic. Cookies can be deleted or rejected by changing the settings on your web browser. However, the deletion or rejection of cookies on a visitor's part may impact your ability to use parts of StateSurge Site effectively. Because advertisers or third party websites may use cookies in different ways, this statement regarding the use of cookies only covers the StateSurge Site. In no way are cookies on the StateSurge Site harmful to the computers on which they are placed or how the information is used.   How do I review and make corrections to my personal information StateSurge members may review and update the personally identifiable information that they have provided to StateSurge by signing into the membership section of the StateSurge Site.   Links to third parties The StateSurge Site may contain links to third-party websites and/or content providers that include information or services that may be of interest to you. This privacy and security statement applies to the StateSurge Site only. This statement does not extend to third-party websites and/or content providers, including related affiliate websites and/or content providers such as section websites, advertiser websites, and third-party service providers. StateSurge is not responsible for the privacy and security practices of those sites. We recommend that you review the privacy policy at each of these websites to determine how that site protects your privacy.
Home
Contact Us
Terms of Usage
Privacy Policy
StateSurge is a non-governmental, non-partisan website. No warranty is made as to the accuracy or timeliness of the data found on this website.
© 2005-2020 LobbyAssist LLC. Patents Pending. All Rights Reserved.
